adtoma.com 2018-02-27

# Privacy Policy – Adtoma AB

## **Signia Group Privacy Policy  **

##### Updated: 6th of July 2016

The Signia Group (Consisting of the companies Signia Creative Intelligence AB, Adtoma AB, Admore Mediasales AB, 500 Magazines AB and Dagens PS AB) is committed to the protection of personal information of the users of its websites. Signia Group Staff and external processors who have access to personal information, and are associated with the processing of that information, are obligated to respect the privacy and confidentiality of information. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the websites operated by the Signia Group in Europe and where the servers are located in Europe.

### What is personal data and other definitions

**Personal data** shall mean any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person; an identifiable person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identification number or to one or more factors specific to his or her physical, physiological, mental, economic, cultural or social identity;

**Processing of personal data** shall mean any operation or set of operations which is performed upon personal data, whether or not by automatic means, such as collection, recording, organization, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination or otherwise making available, alignment or combination, blocking, erasure or destruction.

**The data subject’s consent** shall mean any freely given specific and informed indication of his or her wishes by which the data subject signifies his or her agreement to personal data relating to him or her being processed.

### Information Collection

If you visit Signia Group websites to read or download information, the Signia Group collects and stores only the following information that is automatically recognized: the date and time, the originating IP address, the domain name, the type of browser and operating system used (if provided by the browser), the URL of the referring page (if provided by the browser), the object requested and the completion status of the request.

More information is collected and logged for advanced features, such as placing an order on Signia Group web servers for online payments, downloading, subscribing to a Signia Group newsletter or using the personalization features.

### **  
** Use of Collected Information

Anonymous information is collected from visits to Signia Group websites to measure user activity on these websites. This includes analyzing these logs periodically to measure the traffic through the servers, the number of pages visited and the level of demand for pages and topics of interest, and to help the Signia Group provide better customer service. The logs may be preserved indefinitely and used at any time and in any way to prevent security breaches and to ensure the integrity of the data on the servers. This information is collected through the use of various technologies, including “cookies”.

Moreover, the following information is associated with the cookie: IP address, session number, customer ID (first name, last name and job function) and identification number for online payments, if used. If the user has chosen to “remember login and password”, those two items are encrypted and also associated with the cookie. When a registered user returns to the site without logging in, the ID stored in the cookie is used to track the user (unless the user manually deleted the cookie, at which point the server will automatically create another cookie upon next login if the user choses the “remember login and password” option). If you do not want your transaction details used in this manner, you can disable cookies in your browser. (For more information see Cookie Policy).

Please note that the personal information recorded when you voluntarily registered, is extracted in an anonymous format and then analyzed at an aggregate level to help the Signia Group understand trends and patterns. None of this information is reviewed at an individual level, nor associated with any other personal information.

### How do we treat e-mails you send us?

Many of our web pages have a “Contact” button, which sometimes activates your e-mail software and invites you to send your comments to a specific functional mailbox, or communicate with us.  
When you send such a message, your personal data is collected only to the extent necessary to reply. If the management team of the mailbox is unable to answer your question, it will forward your e-mail to another service.  
If you have any questions about the processing of your e-mail and related personal data, do not hesitate to include them in your message.

### **  
** Your Choice

Registration on Signia Group websites is optional. If you choose not to register or actively provide personal information, you can still use Signia Group websites. However, certain features that require registration may be unavailable (for example, online purchases or e-mail alerts).

Signia Group websites may enable you to communicate with other users and to post information accessible by others. You should be aware that when you choose to use these services, Signia Group has no control over the use of this information by these users.

You may also choose to receive promotional or marketing information from other organizations. When you do so, the Signia Group will only disclose your name and physical and electronic addresses to them. However, you should note that these organizations may follow privacy policies and practices which may be different from those of the Signia Group. At any time you can ask the Signia Group not to further disclose your name and addresses by sending an e-mail to the relevant contacts indicated on the website where you registered.

When you log in to any of the Signia Group websites, Signia Group provides a personalized URL (link) that brings you to a personalized web page. By using this option, you agree to let Signia Group collect information about your session visits. This information helps the Signia Group provide you with information that matches your interests.

### **  
** Links

Throughout the Signia Group websites, you may find links to other third-party websites. Please note that the Signia Group is not responsible for the privacy policies or content on third-party websites.

Signia Group websites may also include links to third-party web servers for online payments, which may have different privacy policies. You are therefore encouraged to review their privacy policies, when visiting these websites.

### How long do we keep your data?

We keep data only as long as necessary for the purpose the data is collected.

### **  
** Individual Access and Right to Correction

You can ask the Signia Group whether it is keeping personal information about you, and you can also request to receive a copy of that personal information. As a safeguard against abuse the Signia Group will ask you to provide proof of your identity before providing you with any personal information. If you are not able to do so, the Signia Group reserves the right to refuse to send you the personal information.

You may request at any time that the Signia Group corrects your personal information in its records. You may also request the deletion of such information, except when it has been collected for a specific purpose for which you have given your consent, for the performance of a contract to which you are a party, or in order to comply with a legal obligation. For such requests, please send an e-mail to the relevant contacts indicated on the website where you registered.

### **  
** Notification of Changes

As the Signia Group creates new services that may generate a need to amend this privacy policy statement, you will find here the previous privacy policy statement.

### Privacy Support

If you have any inquiries about our privacy policy statement, please contact:  
Signia Creative Intelligence AB  
Narvavägen 7, SE-114 60 Stockholm, Sweden  
E-mail: [info@signia.se](mailto:info@signia.se)

This website uses cookies to improve your experience. [Privacy Policy](http://wp-admin.adtoma.com/privacy/) We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. Accept
